module.exports = [
  {
    id: 1,
    database_id: 1,
    question: 'Select all cars that are not older than 10 years and have more than 100k km.',
    answer: 'Select * from cars where date_created >= 2017-01-01 and kilometres > 100000',
    rank: 'easy'
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    database_id: 1,
    question: 'Select * all cars that have more than 4 doors or have top speed over 200 km/h',
    answer: 'Select * from cars where door_count > 4 or top_speed > 200',
    rank: 'easy'
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    database_id: 1,
    question: 'Select all cars that belong to owners from city Rijeka',
    answer: 'Select * from cars t1 join owners t2 on t1.owner_id = t2.id where t2.city = â€˜Rijekaâ€™',
    rank: 'medium'
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    database_id: 1,
    question: 'Select all the Audi models (without duplicates)',
    answer: 'Select distinct(model) from cars where car_brand = â€˜Audiâ€™',
    rank: 'medium'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    database_id: 1,
    question: 'Get the count of cars whose owners are professional drivers',
    answer: 'Select count(*) from cars t1 join owners t2 on t1.owner_id = t2.id where t2.proffesional  = true',
    rank: 'hard'
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    database_id: 1,
    question: 'Get all the owners and count of their cars ordered descending',
    answer: 'Select t2.name, count(*) from cars t1 join owners t2 on t1.owner_id = t2.id  group by t2.id desc',
    rank: 'hard'
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    database_id: 2,
    question: 'Select all boats',
    answer: 'SELECT * FROM boats',
    rank: 'easy'
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    database_id: 2,
    question: 'Select all boats with mileage higher than 10000',
    answer: 'SELECT * FROM boats WHERE mileage>10000',
    rank: 'easy'
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    database_id: 2,
    question: 'Select all Bay boats (no duplicates)',
    answer: 'SELECT * FROM cars',
    rank: 'medium'
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    database_id: 2,
    question: 'Select all boats with mileage higher than 10000',
    answer: 'SELECT * FROM cars WHERE owners>2',
    rank: 'medium'
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    database_id: 2,
    question: 'Select all boats',
    answer: 'SELECT * FROM boats',
    rank: 'hard'
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    database_id: 2,
    question: 'Select all cars with mileage higher than 10000',
    answer: 'SELECT * FROM boats WHERE mileage>10000',
    rank: 'hard'
  }
]
